Andreas Marsh

Computer Science Honors Undergraduate Student

SUMMARY

I am a fourth-year honors student at the University of Georgia studying Computer Science and have training and experience in Java, C++, and Swift programming as well as User Experience Design using Figma and Adobe XD.

I love creating applications that others can interact with and explore and have recently begun the development of a personal website/blog as a side project. Another project I have recently completed was the creation of a Cinema E-Booking system using Java, MySQL, Spring, HTML, and Bootstrap. To complete this, I worked side-by-side with a team of developers to go from creating prototypes of the system to writing the front and backend code. Feel free to check out my GitHub to see these and some of the other projects that I've been working on.

Through years of working at summer camps, I have developed great leadership, communication, and teamwork skills, being able to create environments where everybody feels both included and valued.

EXPERIENCE



Glisson Camp & Retreat Center, Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Counselor*

May 2021 - July 2021 & May 2019 - July 2019

- worked with children and adults with mild to moderate developmental disabilities
- created an environment that uplifted campers and allowed their uniqueness to shine



Glisson Camp & Retreat Center, Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Crew*

May 2018 - July 2018

- performed various jobs and tasks around camp to have it run smoothly
- lifeguarded, helped facilitate high ropes course, set up and cleaned the dining hall, and other jobs
- had a major impact on preparing me for college and how to balance a schedule, work within a group, and gain an overall greater understanding of managing the new independence and responsibilities you're given in college

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATION



The University of Georgia, Athens, GA — BS Computer Science

August 2018 - May 2022



New Media Institute, Athens, GA — *New Media Certificate (Dev Track)*

CONTACT

124 North Poplar St Athens, GA, 30601 (404) 502-0710 marsh.andreas.s@gmail.com

GITHUB / WEBSITE

github.com/andreasmarsh

andreasmarsh.com

SKILLS

Java

C++

Swift

Spring Framework

Android Studio

XCode

Figma

Adobe XD

Bootstrap

HONORS & AWARDS

Honors Program Member of UGA's Honor Program August 2018 - Present

Dean's List Spring Semester 2020

Charter Scholarship Recipient
Awarded for outstanding
achievement in academics to 2%
of new students

LANGUAGES

English (high proficiency)

German (moderate proficiency)